[♪♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
This is my brother George.
[GRUNTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
[SNORTS]
And this is Daddy Pig.
Peppa Pig.
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR: Every morning, Peppa
and George brush their teeth.
[SCRUBBING, BUBBLES POP]
NARRATOR:
Today, Peppa and George
are going to the dentist.
[SNORTS]
Peppa! George!
Are you ready to go
for your checkup?
[GRUNTS]
I'm too busy
for a checkup.
I'm having a tea party
with Teddy.
[IMITATES TEDDY]
Yes, we're very busy.
We all need checkups.
To make sure our teeth
are clean
and healthy.
Okay, Daddy.
[GRUNTS]
George, are your teeth
clean like mine?
NARRATOR:
It is George's first visit
to the dentist.
You both have
lovely, clean teeth.
I'm sure the dentist
will be very happy.
[GIGGLING]
[♪♪♪]
[CAR HORN HONKING]
NARRATOR: Peppa and George
are at the dentist's,
waiting for their checkup.
[CLOCK TICKING]
[YAWNS]
Waiting is boring.
This magazine's
very interesting.
[SNORTS]
It's all about potatoes.
[YAWNING]
Peppa? George? The dentist
will see you now.
Hooray!
[GIGGLES]
NARRATOR:
This is Dr. Elephant,
the dentist.
Hello, Peppa. Have you been
brushing your teeth?
Yes, Dr. Elephant!
Good.
Now, who's first?
I'm first, because
I'm a big girl.
[SNORTS]
Watch me, George!
Sit in the chair,
please.
[GIGGLING]
Hold tight.
[CLICKS LEVER, CHAIR HUMMING]
Wee!
[GIGGLES]
Open wide, please.
Ah.
Wider, please.
Ah!
Now.
Let's take a look.
NARRATOR: Dr. Elephant
uses a little mirror
to look at Peppa's teeth.
I hope you haven't been eating
too many sweeties, Peppa!
[GARBLED TALKING]
NARRATOR:
It is quite difficult to speak
when your mouth is wide open.
[GARBLED TALKING]
[CHUCKLES]
There! All done!
What lovely clean teeth!
She takes after me.
[ALL CHUCKLE]
[GRUNTS]
Can I have the special
pink drink now?
Yes! But don't drink it,
Peppa, spit it out.
[GARGLING]
[ALL GIGGLE]
[SNORTS]
George, now it's your turn.
No.
NARRATOR: George does not
want it to be his turn.
Maybe you can hold
Mr. Dinosaur,
while the dentist
looks at your teeth.
[GIGGLES]
Grrrr! Dine-Saw!
Heh-heh-heh. Very pleased
to meet you, Mr. Dinosaur.
It's not a real dinosaur.
It's made of plastic.
[LAUGHS]
Hold tight.
[CLICKS LEVER, CHAIR HUMMING]
You're doing
very well, George.
Now, can you
show me your teeth?
NARRATOR: George does not want
to show the dentist his teeth.
George, open wide.
Like this...
Ah!
[SNICKERS]
Ah, there they are.
All done.
You have very strong,
clean teeth, George.
Are they as lovely as mine,
Dr. Elephant?
Ah.
Yes.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[GIGGLES, GRUNTS]
NARRATOR: George is very proud
to have clean teeth.
George! Don't forget
the pink drink.
[GARGLING]
Oh, but wait.
What's this?
What's wrong,
Dr. Elephant?
George has clean teeth,
but this young dinosaur's
teeth are very dirty.
Oh no! Dr. Elephant is very
cross with Mr. Dinosaur.
Ha! Ha! Not at all, Peppa.
It's my job to
make teeth clean.
The water jet, please,
Miss Rabbit.
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR: The dentist uses water
to clean Mr. Dinosaur's teeth.
The polisher, please,
Miss Rabbit.
[♪♪♪]
This will be a bit noisy.
[POLISHER CLICKING]
NARRATOR: Dr. Elephant polishes
Mr. Dinosaur's teeth.
Pink! Pink!
That's right, George.
Mr. Dinosaur needs some special
pink drink.
[♪♪♪]
Gosh. What shiny teeth
you have, Mr. Dinosaur.
Grrrrr.
[GIGGLES]
Dine-Saw.
Eek. Too scary.
NARRATOR:
George loves Mr. Dinosaur.
Especially now he has nice,
clean teeth.
[ALL LAUGH]
[KIDS LAUGHING]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR: Peppa and her friends
are going on a school bus trip.
Children. Children.
Attention, please.
Let's check that
you're all here.
Peppa and George.
Here.
[GRUNTS]
Rebecca and
Richard Rabbit?
Here. Squeak.
Squeak, squeak.
Suzy sheep?
Here. Baa...
Zoe Zebra?
Here.
Danny Dog?
Here. Ruff, ruff.
Emily Elephant?
Here.
[TRUMPETS]
[GIGGLES]
Pedro Pony?
NARRATOR:
Pedro Pony is not here.
[BOTH PANTING]
Sorry we're late.
Pedro. You almost
missed the school trip.
Sorry, Madame Gazelle.
Never mind, you're
just in time.
[RINGS BELL]
All aboard.
Neigh.
[GIGGLES]
NARRATOR:
Miss Rabbit is the bus driver.
[RINGS BELL]
Full steam ahead.
ALL:
See you later.
[KIDS GIGGLING]
[ALL CONTINUE GIGGLING]
Children.
Attention, please.
Today, we are going on
a trip to the mountains.
ALL:
Hooray!
MADAME GAZELLE:
Have you all got
your lunchboxes?
ALL:
Yes, Madame Gazelle.
Madame Gazelle, please
can we eat our lunch now?
Peppa. We'll eat lunch when
we arrive in the mountains.
Peppa? What have you got
in your lunchbox?
A red apple.
I've got a green apple.
Let's swap.
Okay.
[BOTH CHUCKLE, CRUNCH]
MADAME GAZELLE:
Peppa. Suzy.
What are you doing?
Suzy told me to open
my lunchbox.
Peppa told me
to swap our apples.
Ho, ho. That's fine.
But please, save some
food for the picnic.
BOTH:
Yes, Madame Gazelle.
[KIDS LAUGHING]
NARRATOR: The bus has arrived
at the foot of the mountains.
[BUS GEARS GRINDING]
NARRATOR:
The mountain road
is very steep.
Come on, bus.
You can make it.
[GEARS GRIND]
ALL: Come on, bus.
KIDS:
Hooray!
[GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her friends are
at the top of the mountain.
[♪♪♪]
Look at the view.
Wow.
[ECHOES]
Who said that?
It's your echo.
What's my echo?
An echo is the sound you hear
when you speak loudly
in the mountains.
Like this.
Yodel-ay-hee-hoo.
[ECHOES]
[GIGGLES, CLEARS THROAT]
Yodel-ay-hee-hoo.
[ECHOES]
[ALL CHUCKLE]
[KIDS SHOUTING]
[ECHOING]
[ALL GIGGLE]
NARRATOR: Echoes are fun.
Time for our picnic.
NARRATOR: Peppa loves picnics.
Everyone loves picnics.
[GRUNTS]
Where are the ducks?
They always turn up
when we have picnics.
Silly Peppa. Ducks don't
live on top of mountains.
[DUCK QUACKS]
Oh.
Quack.
Hello, Mrs. Duck.
Would you like some bread?
[QUACKS]
NARRATOR: The ducks
are very lucky today.
There is lots of bread.
[ALL MUNCHING]
NARRATOR: The ducks are eating
too quickly.
[HICCUPS]
Goodness me.
[BURPS]
[KIDS LAUGH]
[BUS BELL RINGS]
MISS RABBIT: Home time.
All aboard.
NARRATOR:
It's time to go home.
[RINGS BELL]
NARRATOR:
Everybody has had a great time.
[KIDS LAUGHING]
Let's all sing a song.
Can we have
"The Bing Bong Song", please?
Ho, ho.
KIDS: Please, Madame Gazelle,
sing "The Bing Bong Song".
All right.
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ We're playing our tune and
We're singing our song ♪
♪ With a bing and a bong
And a bing ♪
♪ Bong bing boo
Bing bong bing ♪
♪ Bing bong
Bingley bungley booooo ♪
♪ Bong bing boo
Bing bong bing ♪
♪ Bing bong
Bingley bungley booooo. ♪
[KIDS LAUGH]
[MADAME GAZELLE PLAYS GUITAR]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
It is the end of
another lovely day.
[KIDS GIGGLING]
NARRATOR: Peppa and George
are playing with their friends
Rebecca and Richard Rabbit.
Home time,
my little bunnies.
Oh, but we want to
play some more, Mommy.
Maybe tomorrow.
Can Peppa and George
come to our house tomorrow?
Yes.
GIRLS: Hooray!
[GIGGLING]
[CRYING]
Why is Richard crying?
He's a bit scared of
going down stairs.
Why?
We don't have
stairs in our home.
What? No stairs?
That's right. You'll see
tomorrow. Bye bye.
Bye bye.
[SNORTS]
[LAUGHING]
[ENGINE STARTS, HONKS HORN]
[ROOSTER CROWS]
NARRATOR: It is morning,
and Peppa and George
are going to Rebecca Rabbit's
house today.
[GRUNTS]
Mommy Pig can drive and
I'll do the map reading.
MOMMY PIG:
Are you sure, Daddy Pig?
We always get lost when
you do the map reading.
Ha, ha.
We won't get lost.
Okay. Is everybody ready?
[STARTS ENGINE]
Yes, Mommy Pig.
[GEORGE GRUNTS]
Then let's go.
[HONKS HORN]
NARRATOR: Peppa and George
are very excited,
they have never been to
Rebecca Rabbit's house before.
[GRUNTS]
Daddy, are we
nearly there?
The map says Rebecca's house
is on the next hill.
[♪♪♪]
I don't understand. This should
be where Rebecca Rabbit lives.
We must be lost. There's just
this garden of carrots.
NARRATOR: Where can
Rebecca Rabbit's house be?
Squeak. Hello, everyone.
[SQUEAKS]
[CHUCKLING]
Rebecca.
Do you want to play
in my bedroom?
[GRUNTS]
Your bedroom?
But where is your house?
NARRATOR: Peppa cannot see
Rebecca's house anywhere.
This hill is our house.
It's called a burrow.
BOTH: Ooh.
I'll show you.
DADDY PIG:
See you later.
[STARTS ENGINE, HONKS HORN]
Come in.
We don't have stairs,
we have tunnels.
PEPPA & GEORGE:
Wow.
NARRATOR: Rebecca's house is
a bit different to Peppa's.
This is our bedroom.
Wow.
You have a bed, and a window,
and a toybox just like us.
Of course.
[CHUCKLES]
I like your house.
I wish I was a rabbit.
I know. Shall I teach you
both how to be rabbits?
Yes, please.
[SNORTS]
First, you have to twitch
your nose and squeak.
Like this.
[SQUEAKS]
[BOTH SQUEAK]
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Very good, Peppa Rabbit
and George Rabbit.
NARRATOR:
Peppa likes being a rabbit.
George likes being a rabbit.
Rabbits like carrots.
[MUNCHES]
Delicious.
[CRUNCHING]
Yuck.
NARRATOR:
George does not like carrots.
He won't even
try them.
Oh well,
more for us then.
[CRUNCHING]
[GIGGLING]
Rebecca, what else
do rabbits like?
Rabbits like hopping.
Come outside, I'll show you.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Let's hop.
[SQUEAKS]
NARRATOR:
Rabbits like hopping.
[ALL SQUEAK]
You're very
good rabbits.
Lunch time, children.
[KIDS GIGGLE]
NARRATOR:
Mommy and Daddy Rabbit
have prepared lunch.
[SQUEAKS]
Rebecca has taught us
how to be rabbits.
[BOTH SQUEAK]
Ho, ho.
You'll enjoy lunch then,
it's our favorite. Carrots.
Delicious.
Yuck.
George will not
eat carrots.
Oh dear, George,
I thought you were a rabbit.
Rabbits love carrots.
[SQUEAKS, CRUNCHES]
Mm.
[MUNCHING]
Wow. George is eating a carrot.
[LAUGHS]
And this is our favorite cake.
Carrot cake.
[KIDS]
Hooray!
Mm... car-rot cake.
[LAUGHS]
George is a proper rabbit now.
[SQUEAKS]
[ALL GUFFAW]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Today, Peppa and her family
are driving out
to the countryside.
Daddy, what will we see
in the countryside?
[GRUNTS]
We'll see birds and trees
and flowers and bees.
[GIGGLES]
Dine-Saw.
No, George.
I don't think we'll see
any dinosaurs.
[ALL LAUGH]
NARRATOR: This is the start
of the nature trail.
We're here.
Hooray.
Daddy Pig, don't
forget the picnic.
Ho, ho.
As if I would.
Daddy, how do we know
which way to go?
Easy. The map says...
there should be a sign
showing the start of
the nature trail here.
Well done, Daddy Pig.
[KIDS GIGGLE]
NARRATOR: Oh dear, Daddy Pig
has forgotten the picnic.
Peppa, what interesting
things can you see?
Just trees and trees
and more boring trees.
Ha-ha-ha, Peppa, you're
not looking hard enough.
All right.
I'll look really hard
and I still won't see anything.
Oh. What's that?
NARRATOR:
Peppa has found
some footprints.
Whose footprints are these?
Dine-Saw.
Oh George, they're not
dinosaur footprints.
Let's follow the footprints
and see who made them.
Yes.
[GRUNTS]
Shh. We have to be very quiet
so we don't scare anything away.
Yes, Mommy.
George. Shh.
[GIGGLES]
Shh.
NARRATOR: Peppa and George
are following the footprints.
Look.
MOMMY PIG:
The footprints were made
by a little bird.
She's flown into a tree.
Where?
Here, Peppa.
Look through
the binoculars.
NARRATOR: The binoculars make
everything look bigger.
PEPPA:
I can see one, two,
three baby birds.
Aw, I wonder what
they're eating.
Ew!
They're eating worms!
That's disgusting!
[LAUGHING]
[GRUNTS]
NARRATOR: George has found
more footprints.
Ooh.
What little footprints.
DADDY PIG:
The footprint are
being made by ants.
They're collecting
leaves to eat.
Are they going to have
salad for lunch?
[LAUGHING]
Yes.
Talking of lunch,
let's have our picnic.
Oh, the picnic!
Daddy Pig. You've left the
picnic in the car, haven't you?
Uh, yes...
but it's not a problem, we'll
just go back to the car to eat.
But which way is the car?
My map will show us.
[GRUNTS]
This way. Oof.
Who put that tree there?
It's not on the map.
Oh, Daddy Pig.
We're lost, aren't we?
Uh... yes.
[SNORTS]
How are we going to find
our little car?
[GRUNTS]
NARRATOR: George has found
more footprints.
Ooh, what big footprints.
Dine-saw.
Very interesting.
What? Has George found some
real dinosaur footprints?
No, these are
our footprints.
And, if we follow
our footprints,
we'll find the way
back to our car.
And our picnic.
ALL: Hooray!
[GRUNTS, GIGGLES]
DADDY PIG:
Ha, ha. Nothing can stop us
finding our car now.
We're home and dry.
Oh, I wasn't expecting that.
Luckily, I remembered
the umbrella.
NARRATOR: The rain is washing
the footprints away.
How are we going to
find the car now?
And our picnic.
[QUACKING]
It's the ducks.
They always turn up
at picnics.
Sorry, Mrs. Duck, we haven't
got a picnic this time.
We can't find it.
[QUACKS]
I know. Mrs. Duck, can you help
us find our picnic please?
[QUACKING]
[GIGGLES]
[♪♪♪]
We're here.
ALL: Hooray.
Thank you,
Mrs. Duck.
[QUACKS]
[LAUGHS]
[ALL MUNCHING]
I love nature trails.
Yes, and I love picnics.
And the ducks
love picnics.
And the little birds
DADDY PIG:
And the ants love picnics.
Everybody loves picnics.
[ALL LAUGH]
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLING, SNORTING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[GRUNTING, GIGGLING]
[SNORTING, LAUGHING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING]